http://www.alletec.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is Alletec’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://www.alletec.com, and other sites we own and operate.We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.Your InformationWe only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.Information SharingWe don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.Third-Party ResourcesOur website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.Your continued use of our website will be regarded as an acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.Policy UpdatesAlletec reserves the right to update the Privacy Policies if it is required due to new and emerging technologies. Please ensure you have the latest version of our Privacy Policies available. In events of substantial change, we will inform our clients through notifications.This policy is effective as of 1 October 2019.
×
Get In Touch
×
Get In Touch
Solutions & Services
D365 Business Central – NAVD365 Customer EngagementD365 FinanceD365 Supply Chain ManagementMicrosoft Dynamics 365Dynamics GP To D365 BC MigrationSharePoint SolutionsMicrosoft AZURECognitive Services & AIPower Platform
Enter the characters shown in the image:
ASK DYNA
Ask Dyna
